American Association Of University Women
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series X: National, 1951-1988
  - Graduate Woman, 1979-1985 (Box 19:, Folder 396-402)
  - Graduate Woman, 1986-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 403-405)
  - Historical materials, undated (Box 20:, Folder 406)
  - Leader in Action, 1981-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 407)
  - Leader's guide to conducting a workshop, 1983 (Box 20:, Folder 408)
  - Legal Advocacy Fund, 1983 (Box 20:, Folder 409)
  - Legislative history and policy notes, 1970-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 410)
  - Legislative Lookout, 1969-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 411)
  - Legislative program, 1969-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 412)
  - Money Talks, 1981-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 413)
  - National publications, 1957-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 414-415)
  - A New day Beyond ERA, 1982 (Box 20:, Folder 416)
  - President's kit, 1982 (Box 20:, Folder 417)
  - Recruiting materials, 1971-1981 (Box 20:, Folder 418)
  - State President's conference, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 419)
  - Tax reform, 1968-1969 (Box 20:, Folder 420)
  - Technology guide, 1981-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 421)
  - Testing Values in a Changing Society, 1967-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 422)
  - Title IX resource material, 1973-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 423)
  - United Nations, 1973-1981 (Box 20:, Folder 424)
  - Woman's education, 1967-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 425)
  - International
    - Facts About, 1977-1986 (Box 20:, Folder 426)
    - Newsletters, 1960-1985 (Box 20:, Folder 427)
- Series XI: Memorabilia, undated, 1973-1981
  - Convention banners (New Canaan Branch)
    - Connecticut State Flower, 1973 (Box 21:, Folder 428)
    - Centennial Flag, 1975 (Box 21:, Folder 429)
    - Composite of Woman in Woman/Work (Box 21:, Folder 430)
    - Role, 1981
  - Connecticut AAUW banner, undated (Box 22:, Folder 431)
  - Charter Oak Flag, undated (Box 22:, Folder 432)
  - Citations, undated (Box 22:, Folder 433)
  - Miscellaneous items, undated (Box 22:, Folder 434)
  - Paper dolls, 1982 (Box OS)
- Series XII: 1993 Addendum, undated, 1912-1990
  - Administrative
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1977 (Box 23:, Folder 435-442)
    - Branch Membership report, undated (Box 23:, Folder 443)
    - By-Laws, 1958-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 444)
    - By-Laws revisions, undated (Box 23:, Folder 445)
    - Corporate representatives, undated (Box 23:, Folder 446)
    - Fellowship information, undated (Box 23:, Folder 447)
    - General, 1970-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 448-457)
    - Handouts, 1979-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 458)
    - Historical information, undated (Box 23:, Folder 459)
    - Job descriptions, undated (Box 23:, Folder 460)
    - Mailing information, undated (Box 23:, Folder 461)
    - Membership: Perspective, undated (Box 23:, Folder 462)
    - Minutes, 1975-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 463-468)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946-1949 (Box 23:, Folder 469)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960, 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 470)
    - Nestle Boycott, 1979-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 471)
    - New Haven Branch (host CT convention), 1989 (Box 23:, Folder 472)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 23:, Folder 473)
    - Old Branch directories, undated (Box 23:, Folder 474)
    - President: June Onorato, 1979-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 475-477)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 23:, Folder 478)
    - Semi-Centennial Anniversary, 1970 (Box 23:, Folder 479)
    - Tax information, undated (Box 23:, Folder 480)
    - Women in Leadership honoree, 1984 (Box 23:, Folder 481)
  - Branches
    - Clinton
      - Bills, undated (Box 23:, Folder 482)
      - By-Laws, undated (Box 23:, Folder 483)
      - History, undated (Box 23:, Folder 484)
      - Letters, undated (Box 23:, Folder 485)
      - Membership yearbooks, 1949-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 486)
      - Newsletter, undated (Box 24:, Folder 487)
      - Projects, undated (Box 24:, Folder 488)
      - Reports: Officers, chairpersons, undated (Box 24:, Folder 489)
      - Reports to National, undated (Box 24:, Folder 490)
      - Scholarship file, undated (Box 24:, Folder 491)
      - Secretary reports, undated (Box 24:, Folder 492)
      - Taxes, undated (Box 24:, Folder 493)
      - Treasurer's reports, undated (Box 24:, Folder 494)
    - Norwalk
      - Activism, undated (Box 24:, Folder 495)
      - Annual reports, 1938-1947 (Box 24:, Folder 496)
      - Board of Education of CT: A Study of AAAUW, 1941 (Box 24:, Folder 497)
      - Branch history to 1979 (Box 24:, Folder 498)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 24:, Folder 499)
      - Early Days, 1956-1957 (Box 24:, Folder 500)
      - Early years, 1933-1956 (Box 24:, Folder 501)
      - Education correspondence: M. Bernard-Hall, 1948-1960 (Box 24:, Folder 502)
      - Education issues, undated (Box 24:, Folder 503)
      - Family Welfare and Relief project, 1940 (Box 24:, Folder 504)
      - Membership, 1936-1974 (Box 24:, Folder 505)
      - Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 24:, Folder 506)
      - Pre-organization and organization President, undated (Box 24:, Folder 507)
      - President
        - Enid Nash, 1923-1924 (Box 24:, Folder 508)
        - Mrs. A. H. Cole, 1924-1926 (Box 24:, Folder 509)
        - Margaret Brendlinger, 1927-1931 (Box 24:, Folder 510)
        - Marjorie Child, 1931-1933 (Box 24:, Folder 511)
        - Ruth Wilson, 1933-1934 (Box 24:, Folder 512)
        - M. Millar, 1934-1936 (Box 24:, Folder 513)
        - Mary Grumbly, 1936-1938 (Box 24:, Folder 514-515)
        - Mary Rowan, 1938-1940 (Box 24:, Folder 516)
        - Isabel Rock, 1940-1942 (Box 24:, Folder 517)
        - Louise Lemaire, 1943-1944 (Box 24:, Folder 518)
        - M. Bernard, 1944-1946 (Box 24:, Folder 519)
        - Libby Simon, 1946-1948 (Box 24:, Folder 520)
        - Carolyn Hamblen, 1948-1950 (Box 24:, Folder 521)
        - Hester Hall, 1950-1954 (Box 25:, Folder 522)
        - Mary Elizabeth Eames, 1954-1956 (Box 25:, Folder 523)
        - Kathy Bernard, 1956-1958 (Box 25:, Folder 524)
        - Ruth Cowley, 1958-1960 (Box 25:, Folder 525)
        - Sally Bolster, 1960-1962 (Box 25:, Folder 526)
        - B. J. Fannon, 1962-1963 (Box 25:, Folder 527)
        - Marilyn Rothert, 1963-1965 (Box 25:, Folder 528)
        - Ruth Burr, 1965-1967 (Box 25:, Folder 529)
        - Gloria Stewart, 1967-1969 (Box 25:, Folder 530)
        - Clare Mulqueen, 1969-1971 (Box 25:, Folder 531)
        - Valerie Caputo (Acting), 1971-1972 (Box 25:, Folder 532)
        - Valerie Caputo, 1972-1974 (Box 25:, Folder 533)
      - Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Other 1988-0003_1)
      - Survey of Social Agencies, 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 534)
      - Women, 1972-1974 (Box 25:, Folder 535)
    - Norwalk/Westport
      - Board Members, undated (Box 25:, Folder 536)
      - Career Opportunities Study, 1978 (Box 25:, Folder 527)
      - Cultural Interests, undated (Box 25:, Folder 528)
      - Educational Fellowship program, undated (Box 25:, Folder 529)
      - General, undated (Box 25:, Folder 530)
      - Honorees, 1971-1980 (Box 25:, Folder 531)
      - Interest Groups, undated (Box 25:, Folder 532)
      - Member News, undated (Box 25:, Folder 533)
      - Membership, 1970s, 1980s (Box 25:, Folder 534)
      - Membership Booklets, undated (Box 25:, Folder 535)
      - National and International Federation of Uuniversity Women, undated (Box 25:, Folder 536)
      - Newsletters, undated (Box 25:, Folder 537)
      - News letters, 1980s (Box 25:, Folder 538)
      - News clippings, undated (Box 25:, Folder 539)
      - President
        - Gladys Ellenbogen, 1976-1978 (Box 25:, Folder 540)
        - Mary Loughran, 1978-1980 (Box 25:, Folder 541)
        - Laurel Hoffmann, 1980-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 542)
      - Program, undated (Box 26:, Folder 543)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 26:, Folder 544)
      - Publicity, 1952 (Box 26:, Folder 545)
      - Scholarship and Student loan, 1924-1974 (Box 26:, Folder 546)
      - Scholarship fundraiser, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 547)
      - Scholarships, 1970-1990 (Box 26:, Folder 548)
      - Seminar: 1979 Families facing Change (Box 26:, Folder 549)
      - State conference APR, 1990 (Box 26:, Folder 550)
      - Treasurer, 1987-1988 (Box 26:, Folder 551)
      - Women as Agencies of Change, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 552)
      - Women in Local Government, 1970 (Box 26:, Folder 553)
    - Waterbury
      - Annual report, undated (Box 26:, Folder 554)
      - Booklets, 1986-1992 (Box 26:, Folder 555)
      - By-Laws, undated (Box 26:, Folder 556)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 26:, Folder 557)
      - Gift Honoree, 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 558)
      - History, undated (Box 26:, Folder 559)
      - Membership, 1972-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 560)
      - Mentoring skills, undated (Box 26:, Folder 561)
      - Minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 562)
      - News clippings, undated (Box 26:, Folder 563)
      - Newsletter, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 564)
      - Proclamation, 1985 (Box 26:, Folder 565)
      - Publicity, 1967-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 566)
      - Record Book, 1912-1935 (Box 26:, Folder 567)
      - Secretary's Records, 1912-1919 (Box 26:, Folder 568)
      - Secretary's Records, 1944-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 569-575)
      - Yearbooks, 1936-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 576)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Norwalk, 1935-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 577-584)
    - Waterbury, 1953-1992 (Box 28:, Folder 585-594)
    - Equal Right Amendment, 1973-1986 (Box 29:, Folder 595-596)
  - Publications
    - Many a Good Crusade, Virginia Crocheron Gildersleeve, 1954 (Box 30:, Folder 597)
    - Book Review, New York Herald, 1954 (Box 30:, Folder 598)
- Series XIII: 1996 Addendum, undated, 1960s-1990s
  - Fliers, publications, notes, clippings, administrative and financial records, correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 1996_1)
    [Subjects include: Organization publications.]
  - Notes, fliers, administrative and financial records, publications, correspondence, realia, 1970s-1980s (Box 1996_2)
    [Subjects include: General operations.]
  - Fliers, photocopies, book, clippings, notes, scrapbooks, 1960s-1990s (Box 1996_3)
    [Subjects include: Organizational publications and memorabilia.]
- Series XIV: 1998-2010 Addenda, undated, 1940s-2005
  - Fliers, administrative records, postcard, publications, clippings, award, correspondence, 1950s-1990s (Box 1)
    [Subjects include: Danbury branch.]
  - Scrapbook, 1970-1982 (Box 2)
    [Subjects include: Ridgefield branch.]
  - Books, scrapbook, publication, fliers, 1980s-1990s (Box 3)
  - Administrative and financial records, fliers, publications, scrapbook, photograph, 1990s (Box 4)
  - Scrapbooks, 1990-2000 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, administrative records, publications, clippings, fliers, photographs, notes, scrapbooks, 1984-2005 (Box 6)
    [Subjects include: Norwalk-Westport branch programs/ activities, minutes/reports.]
  - Legal documents, administrative and financial records, ublications, correspondence, notes, fliers, clippings, 1980s-2005 (Box 7)
    [Subjects include: Norwalk-Westport branch report, programs; Stamford branch directories.]
  - Artwork, 1994-1996 (Box 8)
    [Subjects include: Norwalk-Westport branch banner.]
  - Administrative and financial records, fliers, notes, correspondence, ephemera, sound recording, 1990-2000 (Box 9)
    [Subjects include: CT-state division administration.]
  - Scrapbook, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
    [Subjects include: Greater Waterbury branch.]
  - Scrapbook, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1994-1997 (Box 12)
  - Publications, fliers, clippings, administrative and financial records, correspondence, notes, postcards, awards, map, photographs, prints, 1980s-1990s (Box 13)
    [Subjects include: Greenwich branch .]
  - Administrative and financial records, notes, legal records, correspondence, fliers, ephemera, publications, poster, photographs, prints, clippings, moving images, 1970s-2000s (Box 14)
  - Photographs, prints, book, financial records, 1957-1960, 2000-2002 (Box 15)
  - Administrative and financial records, clipping, scrapbook, clippings, photographs, postcard, awards, publications, 1940-1980s (Box 16)
    [Subjects include: Greenwich branch.]
  - Scrapbook, 1994 (Box 17)
    [Subjects include: Waterbury branch year book.]
  - Administrative and financial records, books, note, correspondence, fliers, ephemera, publications, poster, 1980s, 2000-2003 (Box 18)
    [Subjects include: State division report, and other branches--Storrs, Willimantic, Stamford, Norwalk, Westport, Stamford, Darien.]
  - Fliers, photographs, clippings, publication, scrapbook, 1980s-1990s (Box 19)
  - Ephemera, book, administrative and financial records, correspondence, postcards, notes, clippings, publications, fliers, photographs, 1980s-1990s (Box 20)
    [Subjects include: Norwalk- Westport branch.]
  - Administrative and financial records, notes, fliers, correspondence, publications, notes, book, photographs, clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 21)
    [Subjects include: Norwalk-Westport branch, CT State division, and other branches' publications.]